# Suyeong Park

suyeong.park0@gmail.com — github.com/euphoria0-0

# Research Interest

My Research interests are mainly on making more **Trustworthy AI** using collaborations of information in data and knowledge from human-beings. I mainly focused on estimating uncertainty on Bayesian approach, especially 'what information we need between **representativity and uncertainty** for better ML model'. Currently, I believe 'understanding an intrinsic attributes of things using our knowledge' is crucial for deploying ML models for better human-being life in a real-world. Thus, I'm currently interested in identifying CAUSALITY of things from our data for explainable AI while overcoming the limitations of typical ML.

#### EDUCATION

#### Ulsan National Institute of Science and Technology (UNIST)

Ulsan, Korea

Master of Science in Artificial Intelligence

Aug. 2020 - Aug. 2022

GPA: 4.15/4.3

Advisor: Prof. Kwang In Kim and Prof. Namhoon Lee

Thesis: Active Client Selection for Communication-efficient Federated Learning [Link]

Relevant Coursework: Causal Learning & Explainable AI, Reinforcement Learning, Advanced Machine Learning Topics

University of Seoul

Seoul, Korea

Bachelor of Science in Statistics and Data Science

Mar. 2015 - Feb 2020

Apr. 2020 – Jun. 2020

Jan. 2020 - Feb. 2020

GPA: 3.7/4.5

Relevant Coursework: Bayesian Statistics, Machine Learning, Deep Learning, Time Series Analysis, Multivariate Statistics, Statistical Computing, Linear Algebra, Probability Theory, Mathematical Statistics

# E

Experience	
Visiting Researcher  CausalML Lab, Purdue University (supervised by Prof. Dr. Murat Kocaoglu)	Jul. 2022 - Aug. 2022 West Lafayette, USA
<ul> <li>Research Project: Bayesian Causal Discovery</li> <li>Research Assistant</li> <li>Machine Learning and Vision Lab, UNIST (supervised by Prof. Dr. Kwang In Kim)</li> <li>Research Projects: active learning, transfer learning, federated learning, image attribute</li> </ul>	Aug. 2020 – Aug. 2022 <i>Ulsan, Korea</i> te estimation
<ul> <li>Intern, Data Analyst and Engineer</li> <li>Seoul Big Data Campus</li> <li>Projects: Citizen Movement and Consumption Behaviour analysis around Seoul city</li> </ul>	Mar. 2020 - Jun. 2020 Seoul, Korea
<ul> <li>Intern, Data Analyst Assistant</li> <li>FSC (Financial Services Commission)</li> <li>Projects: Data analysis using financial public data</li> </ul>	Sep. 2019 - Feb. 2020 Seoul, Korea
Publication	
S. Park, Y. Ahn, K. Kim. Blind (keyword: Deep Active Learning, Bayesian Approach) PROJECTS	In Submission., 2022
Visual Common Sense Through Self-supervised Learning for Restoration of Invisible Parts in Image  • Image Attribute Recognition	April 2021 – Present
Causal Learning with Artificial Intelligence	Mar. 2021 – Dec. 2021

Financial data analysis using financial public data • Data analysis with financial public dataset in FSC

Citizen Movement and Consumption Behaviour analysis around Seoul city

• Data analysis with card consumption, moving population data by Seoul city region

• Causal Discovery with genome data

# TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: Python, R, SQL (MySQL)

Frameworks: PyTorch, TensorFlow, Scipy, Matplotlib Developer Tools: Git, Docker, PyCharm, VSCode

Others: QGIS, Tableau, SAS

#### Talks and Teaching

#### **Guest Talk**

# CSE362 Artificial Intelligence, Department of CSE, UNIST

Nov. 2021

Introduction to Federated Learning (for undergraduate students)

# Teaching Assistant

# AI519 Advanced Machine Learning Topics, AI Graduate School, UNIST

Fall. 2021

 $Cusco, \ Peru$ 

#### Extra-curricular Experience

### **Exchange Student**

Jun. 2018 - Aug. 2018

Universidad San Ignacio De Loyola

• Coursework: Spanish, Photograph

#### Exchange Student

Aug. 2017 - Feb. 2018 The Hague, Netherlands

 $The \ Hague \ University \ of \ Applied \ Sciences$ 

• Coursework: User Experience Design, Design Programming

Last Updated: September 14, 2022